{
    "subject": "Warren_Beatty",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Love_Affair__1994_film_",
    "human_readable": "Warren Beatty produced the film Love Affair (1994).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9423754811286926,
            "question": "Who produced the film Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.814923882484436,
            "question": "Was Love Affair (1994) a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7939611673355103,
            "question": "What genre is the film Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7135282754898071,
            "question": "What year was the film Love Affair released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6848465204238892,
            "question": "Who were some of the actors in Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6071014404296875,
            "question": "Has Warren Beatty produced any other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5225453972816467,
            "question": "What themes are explored in Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5126819014549255,
            "question": "What is Warren Beatty known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4378611147403717,
            "question": "Is there a different version of the film Love Affair?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29924917221069336,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Warren Beatty's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warren Beatty produced the film Love Affair (1994).",
            "html": "yago_21514_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a different version of the film Love Affair?",
            "html": "yago_21514_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Warren Beatty known for?",
            "html": "yago_21514_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes are explored in Love Affair (1994)?",
            "html": "yago_21514_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21514_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The files mention that the movie \"Love Affair\" was released in 1994 and directed by Glenn Gordon Caron, but one of the files mentions that Warren Beatty produced the film from a screenplay by Robert Towne and Beatty."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that the film \"Love Affair\" was produced by Warren Beatty. Therefore, the triple \"Warren Beatty produced the film Love Affair (1994)\" is correct according to the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}